Wilcox College of Nursing Records
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series IV: Press Materials and Photographs, undated, 1909-1997
  - Photographs (not from Scrapbooks)
    - Front View of Middlesex Hospital, 1915 (Box 69:, Folder 887)
    - Hospital Day, circa 1920 (Box 69:, Folder 888)
    - Pharmacy, 1920 (Box 69:, Folder 889)
    - Setting the table, 1920 (Box 69:, Folder 890)
    - Nurses Studying, 1920 (Box 69:, Folder 891)
    - Bengston-Wood Hall, 1929 (Box 69:, Folder 892)
    - (2) Packard Ambulance, 1936 (Box 69:, Folder 893)
    - Officer giving public speech, circa 1940s (Box 69:, Folder 894)
    - Dr. Willard Buckley with Interns, 1941 (Box 69:, Folder 895)
    - Bacteriology Analysis, 1942 (Box 69:, Folder 896)
    - (3) Gifts for 100th Baby, Proclamation, & Presentation, 1942 October (Box 69:, Folder 897)
    - Admitting Office, 1943 (Box 69:, Folder 898)
    - Kathryn Closson & Bernard C. Dyer, 1943 (Box 69:, Folder 899)
    - Boiler Room, 1944 (Box 69:, Folder 900)
    - Cashier, 1944 (Box 69:, Folder 901)
    - Hospital Board Meeting, 1945 (Box 69:, Folder 902)
    - Henry H. Lyman -president of hospital, 1946 (Box 69:, Folder 903)
    - Infant Ward, circa 1950 (Box 69:, Folder 904)
    - (2)Overhead view of school / hospital, Entrance, circa 1950 (Box 69:, Folder 905)
    - Construction, circa 1950s (Box 69:, Folder 906)
    - Henry Lyman officiating, 1951 Junee7 (Box 69:, Folder 907)
    - 2 Photos of Construction, 1951 July 26 (Box 69:, Folder 908)
    - Nurses & DOctoberor's at Work, 1952 (Box 69:, Folder 909)
    - South Wing Construction, 1952 April (Box 69:, Folder 910)
    - Betty Lon Keech &?, 1954 (Box 69:, Folder 911)
    - Construction, 1968 May (Box 69:, Folder 912)
    - Operating Room, 1970 (Box 69:, Folder 913)
    - Photo of Middlesex Hospital, 1994 (Box 69:, Folder 914)
    - Photo of Graduation, 1995 June (Box 69:, Folder 915)
    - Nurses Class Photo & picture of framed photo, 1909 (Box 70:, Folder 916)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1910 (Box 70:, Folder 917)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1912 (Box 70:, Folder 918)
    - Nurses Class Photo- graduation day, 1912 (Box 70:, Folder 919)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1913 (Box 70:, Folder 920)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1914 (Box 70:, Folder 921)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1915 (Box 70:, Folder 922)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1916 (Box 70:, Folder 923)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1920 (Box 70:, Folder 924)
    - Nurses Class Photo & reproduction of photo, 1921 (Box 70:, Folder 925)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1922 (Box 70:, Folder 926)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1923 (Box 70:, Folder 927)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1924 (Box 70:, Folder 928)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1925 (Box 70:, Folder 929)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1926 (Box 70:, Folder 930)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1927 (Box 70:, Folder 931)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1928 (Box 70:, Folder 932)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1929 (Box 70:, Folder 933)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1930 (Box 70:, Folder 934)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1931 (Box 70:, Folder 935)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1932 (Box 70:, Folder 936)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1933 (Box 70:, Folder 937)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1934 (Box 70:, Folder 938)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1935 (Box 70:, Folder 939)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1936 (Box 70:, Folder 940)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1937 (Box 70:, Folder 941)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1938 (Box 70:, Folder 942)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1939 (Box 70:, Folder 943)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1940 (Box 70:, Folder 944)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1942 (Box 70:, Folder 945)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1943 (Box 70:, Folder 946)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1944 (Box 70:, Folder 947)
    - Volunteer Red Cross Nurses Aides, 1944 (Box 70:, Folder 948)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1945 (Box 70:, Folder 949)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1946 (Box 70:, Folder 950)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1947 (Box 70:, Folder 951)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1948 (Box 70:, Folder 952)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1949 (Box 70:, Folder 953)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1950 (Box 70:, Folder 954)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1951 (Box 70:, Folder 955)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1952 (Box 70:, Folder 956)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1955 (Box 70:, Folder 957)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1957 (Box 70:, Folder 958)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1959 (Box 70:, Folder 959)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1964 (Box 70:, Folder 960)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1965 (Box 70:, Folder 961)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1967 (Box 70:, Folder 962)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1968 (Box 70:, Folder 963)
    - Nurses Class Photo, 1970 (Box 70:, Folder 964)
    - Negative of class picture, 1979 (Box 70:, Folder 965)
  - Slides
    - Proofs- 4 sheets, circa 1980s (Box 71:, Folder 966)
    - Miscellaneous slides- 16 full sheets, 1 w/ 19 filled, Various dates (Box 71:, Folder 967)
  - Photos (Large)
    - Class Photo- U.S. Cadet Nurse Corps, undated (Box 72:, Folder 968)
    - Class Photo, 1954 (Box 72:, Folder 969)
    - Class Photo, 1956 (Box 72:, Folder 970)
    - Class Photo, 1958 (Box 72:, Folder 971)
    - Class Photo, 1971 (Box 72:, Folder 972)
    - Class Photo, 1972 (Box 72:, Folder 973)
    - Class Photo, 1973 (Box 72:, Folder 974)
    - Class Photo, 1975 (Box 72:, Folder 975)
    - Class Photo, 1976 (Box 72:, Folder 976)
    - Class Photo, 1977 (Box 72:, Folder 977)
    - Class Photo, 1978 (Box 72:, Folder 978)
    - Class Photo, 1983 (Box 72:, Folder 979)
    - Class Photo, 1984 (Box 72:, Folder 980)
    - Class Photo, 1985 (Box 72:, Folder 981)
    - Class Photo, 1986 (Box 72:, Folder 982)
    - Class Photo, 1987 (Box 72:, Folder 983)
    - Class Photo, 1988 (Box 72:, Folder 984)
    - Fordham Hospital Doctor, NY, 1914 December 27 (Box 72:, Folder 985)
    - Ambulance, circa 1910 (Box 72:, Folder 986)
    - Diploma of Marchy Adeline Bolan, 1914 March (Box 73:, Folder 987)
    - Play- “Pageant”, circa 1920 (Box 73:, Folder 988)
    - Class Photo, 1923 (Box 73:, Folder 989)
    - Class Photo, 1960 (Box 73:, Folder 990)
    - Class Photo, 1961 (Box 73:, Folder 991)
    - Class Photo, 1962 (Box 73:, Folder 992)
    - Class Photo, 1963 (Box 73:, Folder 993)
    - Class Photo, 1969 (Box 73:, Folder 994)
    - Class Photo, 1974 (Box 73:, Folder 995)
    - Class Photo, 1980 (Box 74:, Folder 996)
    - Class Photo, 1981 (Box 74:, Folder 997)
    - Class Photo, 1982 (Box 74:, Folder 998)
    - Class Photo, 1989 (Box 74:, Folder 999)
    - Class Photo (Evening), 1990 (Box 74:, Folder 1000)
    - Class Photo, 1991 (Box 74:, Folder 1001)
    - Class Photo, 1991 (Box 74:, Folder 1002)
    - Class Photo (Evening/Day), 1995/1996 (Box 74:, Folder 1003)
    - Oversize
    - Class Photo (Evening), 1997 (Box 75:, Folder 1004)
    - Class Photo, 1997 (Box 75:, Folder 1005)
    - Class Photo, 1995 (Box 75:, Folder 1006)
    - Class Photo (Day/Evening), 1994/1993 (Box 75:, Folder 1007)
    - Class Photo, 1993 (Box 75:, Folder 1008)
    - Class Photo, 1992 (Box 75:, Folder 1009)
    - Class Photo, 1953 (Box 75:, Folder 1010)
- Series V: Memorabilia, undated, 1947-2007
  - Nursing Uniforms (Box 76)
    - “Miss R. Zimmer” -striped uniform, undated
    - Top & Bottom -striped uniform, undated
    - Sleeves & White Uniform w/ patch, undated
    - White uniform w/ patch, undated
    - “Michaud” white uniform with patch, undated
    - “DeStephani” blue gown, undated
    - “Miss M. Poelman” uniform- striped w/ white, undated
    - Striped w/ white uniform - w/ patch, undated
    - Blue gown- “Dolores L. Bradley”, undated
    - Two unidentified nursing uniforms, undated
  - Nursing Coats & Caps (Box 77)
    - 2 Coats, 4 caps, undated
  - Other Memorabilia (Box 78)
    - Marchy B. Heath framed poem, 1995
    - Framed painting of nursing lantern emblem, 1947?
    - 2 Doll size Nursing Caps, undated
    - China Nursing Lantern, undated
    - Plaque, Eve1992
    - Wilcox Flag, undated
    - 3 Graduation Pins, undated
    - 2 E. Kent Hubbard Pins, circa 1970
    - Eagle Pin, undated
    - 4 Pharmacy Pins, undated
    - Medal, undated
    - 2 Cross Pins, undated
    - 2 pins, Middlesex Memorial Hospital School of Nursing, circa 1960
  - Oversize (Box 79)
    - Doll in Wilcox uniform [65KB .jpg file]
    - Gertrude Ida Coombs memorabilia, 1923 (Box 80)
      - Diploma, Graduation exercises program, pin
  - Reunion materials (50th), 2007 (Box 81)
- Series VI: Audiovisual materials, 1993-1996
  - Video cassettes
    - Ona M. Wilcox College of Nursing. Wilcox Class of 1994: pinning ceremony; graduation ceremony (Other Video 190)
    - Ona M. Wilcox College of Nursing. Wilcox Class of 1994: pinning ceremony; graduation ceremony (Other Video 191)
    - Thelma Young's retirement party, WCN, 5-6-96; excerpts from T. Young's demonstrations, skill [?] lab, [1996] (Other Video 195)
    - Ona Wilcox pinning, 1993 June 4 (Other Video 196)